<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on </title>
    <link>/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with PLX.IE</title>
      <link>/docs/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;your-journey-to-the-cloud-starts-here&#34;&gt;Your Journey to the Cloud Starts Here&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to PLX.IE! This guide will help you set up your account, deploy your first application, and begin leveraging our powerful cloud services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-account-setup&#34;&gt;1. Account Setup&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;11-create-your-account&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.1 Create Your Account&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Visit our &lt;a href=&#34;https://plx.ie/signup&#34;&gt;sign-up page&lt;/a&gt; and follow the prompts to create your PLX.IE account. You&amp;rsquo;ll need a valid email address and a strong password.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;12-verify-your-email&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.2 Verify Your Email&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After signing up, a verification email will be sent to your registered address. Click the link in the email to activate your account.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internal Guidelines</title>
      <link>/docs/internal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/internal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;plxie-internal-guidelines--best-practices&#34;&gt;PLX.IE Internal Guidelines &amp;amp; Best Practices&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This document outlines key internal guidelines and best practices for all PLX.IE employees. Adhering to these principles ensures consistency, efficiency, and maintains the high standards of our operations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-communication-protocols&#34;&gt;1. Communication Protocols&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;11-slack-usage&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.1 Slack Usage&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Channels:&lt;/strong&gt; Use public channels for team-wide discussions and project-specific communication. Create private channels only when strictly necessary for sensitive information.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Threads:&lt;/strong&gt; Always use threads for replies to keep conversations organized and easy to follow.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notifications:&lt;/strong&gt; Configure your notifications to avoid distractions while staying informed. Use &lt;code&gt;@here&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;@channel&lt;/code&gt; sparingly and only for urgent, team-wide announcements.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;12-email-etiquette&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.2 Email Etiquette&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professionalism:&lt;/strong&gt; Maintain a professional tone in all email communications.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clarity &amp;amp; Conciseness:&lt;/strong&gt; Be clear and to the point. Use bullet points for readability.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Response Times:&lt;/strong&gt; Aim to respond to internal emails within 24 hours and external emails within 48 hours during business days.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-code-development--review&#34;&gt;2. Code Development &amp;amp; Review&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;21-version-control-git&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.1 Version Control (Git)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Branching Strategy:&lt;/strong&gt; Follow the GitFlow branching model for feature development, releases, and hotfixes.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Commit Messages:&lt;/strong&gt; Write clear, concise, and descriptive commit messages. Use a conventional commit format (e.g., &lt;code&gt;feat: Add new feature&lt;/code&gt;, &lt;code&gt;fix: Resolve bug&lt;/code&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pull Requests (PRs):&lt;/strong&gt; All code changes must go through a pull request review process. Ensure your PRs are small, focused, and include relevant tests.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;22-code-quality&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.2 Code Quality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Linting &amp;amp; Formatting:&lt;/strong&gt; Adhere to project-specific linting rules and code formatting standards (e.g., Prettier, ESLint, Black).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Testing:&lt;/strong&gt; Write comprehensive unit, integration, and end-to-end tests for all new features and bug fixes. Aim for high test coverage.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation:&lt;/strong&gt; Document complex code, APIs, and architectural decisions. Keep READMEs updated.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-security-best-practices&#34;&gt;3. Security Best Practices&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;31-password-management&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.1 Password Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Use strong, unique passwords for all PLX.IE accounts.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Utilize our approved password manager for storing and sharing credentials securely.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Enable Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) wherever possible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;32-data-handling&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.2 Data Handling&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Do not store sensitive customer data on local machines.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Access production systems only when necessary and with proper authorization.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Report any suspected security incidents immediately to the security team.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-meeting-guidelines&#34;&gt;4. Meeting Guidelines&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agendas:&lt;/strong&gt; All meetings should have a clear agenda distributed beforehand.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Start and end meetings on time. Respect everyone&amp;rsquo;s schedule.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action Items:&lt;/strong&gt; Clearly define action items and assign owners and deadlines at the end of each meeting.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-professional-development&#34;&gt;5. Professional Development&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PLX.IE encourages continuous learning. Employees are allocated a budget for conferences, online courses, and certifications. Discuss your development goals with your manager during performance reviews.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Operational Processes</title>
      <link>/docs/processes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/processes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;plxie-operational-processes&#34;&gt;PLX.IE Operational Processes&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This document outlines key operational processes within PLX.IE, ensuring smooth and efficient workflows across various departments. Adherence to these processes is crucial for maintaining service quality, security, and compliance.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-incident-management-process&#34;&gt;1. Incident Management Process&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;11-incident-detection--reporting&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.1 Incident Detection &amp;amp; Reporting&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Automated Monitoring:&lt;/strong&gt; All critical systems are monitored 24/7 by automated tools (e.g., Prometheus, Grafana, ELK Stack) for anomalies and errors.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;User Reporting:&lt;/strong&gt; Customers and internal teams can report incidents via the support portal, email, or dedicated communication channels.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Severity Levels:&lt;/strong&gt; Incidents are categorized by severity (P1-P4) based on impact to customers and business operations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;12-incident-response--resolution&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.2 Incident Response &amp;amp; Resolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;On-Call Rotation:&lt;/strong&gt; Dedicated on-call engineers are alerted immediately for P1/P2 incidents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Triage &amp;amp; Diagnosis:&lt;/strong&gt; The incident response team quickly triages, diagnoses the root cause, and identifies a mitigation strategy.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication:&lt;/strong&gt; Regular updates are provided to affected customers and internal stakeholders via status pages and communication channels.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resolution &amp;amp; Verification:&lt;/strong&gt; Once a fix is implemented, it is thoroughly verified before the incident is closed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;13-post-incident-review-pir&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.3 Post-Incident Review (PIR)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blameless Culture:&lt;/strong&gt; PIRs are conducted for all P1/P2 incidents to identify contributing factors and lessons learned, focusing on systemic improvements rather than individual blame.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Action Items:&lt;/strong&gt; Concrete action items are assigned to prevent recurrence, improve detection, and enhance response capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentation:&lt;/strong&gt; PIR reports are documented and shared internally for knowledge sharing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-change-management-process&#34;&gt;2. Change Management Process&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;21-change-request-cr-submission&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.1 Change Request (CR) Submission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All proposed changes to production systems (infrastructure, code, configuration) must be submitted as a formal Change Request.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CRs must include a detailed description, justification, rollback plan, and impact assessment.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;22-review--approval&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.2 Review &amp;amp; Approval&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;CRs are reviewed by relevant stakeholders (e.g., engineering leads, security, operations) based on their potential impact.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;High-risk changes require multiple levels of approval.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changes are scheduled during designated maintenance windows to minimize disruption.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;23-implementation--verification&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.3 Implementation &amp;amp; Verification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Changes are implemented by authorized personnel following documented procedures.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Post-implementation verification steps are executed to ensure the change was successful and did not introduce new issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;24-rollback-plan&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.4 Rollback Plan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;A clear and tested rollback plan must be in place for every change, allowing for quick reversion in case of unforeseen issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-customer-onboarding-process&#34;&gt;3. Customer Onboarding Process&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;31-initial-contact--needs-assessment&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.1 Initial Contact &amp;amp; Needs Assessment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sales team engages with potential customers to understand their requirements and identify suitable PLX.IE services.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Solution architects may be involved for complex technical discussions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;32-account-provisioning--setup&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.2 Account Provisioning &amp;amp; Setup&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Once a service agreement is in place, the customer success team initiates account provisioning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Necessary resources (e.g., cloud instances, databases, API keys) are set up according to the customer&amp;rsquo;s plan.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;33-onboarding--training&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.3 Onboarding &amp;amp; Training&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Customers receive access to our comprehensive documentation and getting started guides.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Dedicated onboarding sessions and technical training may be provided for enterprise clients.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Introduction to the customer support channels and dedicated account managers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;34-ongoing-support--relationship-management&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.4 Ongoing Support &amp;amp; Relationship Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Regular check-ins by customer success managers to ensure customer satisfaction and identify opportunities for further value.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;24/7 technical support available for any operational issues.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Security Best Practices</title>
      <link>/docs/security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/docs/security/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;plxie-security-best-practices&#34;&gt;PLX.IE Security Best Practices&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At PLX.IE, security is paramount. This document outlines the best practices and guidelines that all employees must adhere to to protect our systems, data, and customers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-data-protection&#34;&gt;1. Data Protection&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;11-data-classification&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.1 Data Classification&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All data handled by PLX.IE is classified based on its sensitivity (e.g., Public, Internal, Confidential, Restricted).&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Employees must understand and adhere to the handling requirements for each data classification.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;12-data-encryption&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.2 Data Encryption&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All sensitive data at rest and in transit must be encrypted using approved cryptographic standards.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ensure proper key management practices are followed for all encryption keys.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;13-data-minimization&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.3 Data Minimization&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Collect and retain only the data necessary for business operations and legal compliance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Regularly review and purge unnecessary data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-access-control&#34;&gt;2. Access Control&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;21-principle-of-least-privilege&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.1 Principle of Least Privilege&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Employees are granted access only to the systems and data required to perform their job functions.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Access rights are reviewed periodically and revoked when no longer needed.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;22-strong-authentication&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.2 Strong Authentication&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All internal and external systems require strong, unique passwords.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) is mandatory for all access to sensitive systems and data.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;23-session-management&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2.3 Session Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Implement secure session management practices, including session timeouts and secure cookie handling.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;3-system--network-security&#34;&gt;3. System &amp;amp; Network Security&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;31-patch-management&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.1 Patch Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All systems (servers, workstations, network devices) must be kept up-to-date with the latest security patches and software updates.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Automated patching solutions are preferred where feasible.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;32-network-segmentation&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.2 Network Segmentation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Networks are segmented to isolate critical systems and data, limiting the blast radius of potential breaches.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Firewall rules are strictly enforced to control traffic flow between segments.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;33-vulnerability-management&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3.3 Vulnerability Management&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Regular vulnerability scans and penetration tests are conducted on our applications and infrastructure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Identified vulnerabilities are prioritized and remediated in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;4-employee-responsibilities&#34;&gt;4. Employee Responsibilities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Security Awareness Training:&lt;/strong&gt; All employees must complete mandatory security awareness training annually.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phishing Awareness:&lt;/strong&gt; Be vigilant against phishing attempts and report any suspicious emails immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Clean Desk Policy:&lt;/strong&gt; Ensure sensitive information is not left exposed on desks or unattended workstations.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reporting Incidents:&lt;/strong&gt; Report any suspected security incidents, breaches, or policy violations to the security team immediately.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;5-incident-response&#34;&gt;5. Incident Response&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Familiarize yourself with the Incident Management Process outlined in the Operational Processes documentation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Understand your role in responding to security incidents.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
